<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About Automic's CA Agile Central Package
================================
CA Agile Central is an enterprise-class platform that's purpose-built for scaling agile development practices. It provides a hub for teams to collaboratively plan, prioritize and track work on a synchronized cadence. With this package we automate the following:
* Create/Edit/Bulk edit/Delete a user story.
* Add attachment/comment to the work item.
* Export the work items

=Supported CA Agile Central versions=
v2.0

=Setup=
* This action pack supports Windows as well as UNIX Agent OS.
* Oracle JRE 1.7 or higher must be installed on Agent OS and "java" must be set as executable on the same.
* The Agent should be able to access CA Agile Central rest api endpoint URL in order to make HTTP(s) requests.
* Connection details for Agile Central should be known to the user.

=Variables=
PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.VARA.PACKAGE_PARAMETERS
* API version and https port can be configured in this VARA based on your environment.

=Actions=
Following actions are supported for CA AGILE CENTRAL.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_USER_STORY 
* Action Description: This action deletes the given user story along with the tasks associated to it.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_USER_STORY
* Action Description: This action creates a new user story.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.EDIT_USER_STORY
* Action Description: This action edits a user story.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.BULK_EDIT_USER_STORIES
* Action Description: This action edits one or more user stories.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.ADD_COMMENT
* Action Description: This action adds the comment to provided work Item.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.CHANGE_USER_STORY_STATUS
* Action Description: This action changes the status of provided user story.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_AGILECENTRAL.PUB.ACTION.ADD_ATTACHMENT
* Action Description: This action adds file attachment to provided work Item.

]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>